♪ We
♪ Are the Crystal
♪ Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
♪ And if you think we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
♪ Amethyst
♪ And Pearl
And Steven!
史蒂文 我们不能同时存在
Steven, we can't both exist.
我将会成为你的一半
I'm going to become half of you.
我想要你明白
And I need you to know
你热爱自己的存在的每一刻
that every moment you love being yourself,
那也都是我在爱你
that's me, loving you,
也爱成为你...
and loving being you...
因为你注定会成为非同寻常的存在
because you're going to be something extraordinary.
你注定会成为...
You're going to be...
你注定会成为非同寻常的存在
You're going to be something extraordinary.
非同寻常...体验
Extraordinary... experience.
好 我找到了些线索
Okay, I think I've got something.
这次呢 我把每一句话
So, this time, I put together the first letter
首字母放在一起
of the first word of every sentence.
拼出来“Ittaisiaby”
It spells "Ittaisiaby."
也许听起来没什么
It might not sound like much,
但是重新排列一下这些字母
but if you rearrange those letters,
就会得到“Bait it I say”或者“I stay a bit”
it says "Bait it I say," or "I stay a bit,"
或者“I bitty Asia(我点点亚洲)”
or "I bitty Asia."
可能“我点点亚洲”有些道理
Well "I bitty Asia" could mean something.
可能我得再回亚洲一次?
Maybe I'm supposed to go back to Asia?
然后...咬什么东西?
And... bite something?
不管 在哪 肯定有些线索的
There has to be a clue somewhere.
妈妈说她想要我存在
Mom said she wanted to have me.
这肯定意味着我的存在是有目的的
But that must mean there's a reason.
肯定有些事要我来完成
There has to be something I was meant to do.
我得魔法宝石宿命
My magical gem destiny.
拜托 狮子 专心听我讲
Come on, Lion. I need you to focus here.
别 别 别!
No, no, no!
狮子 要吐也吐地板上啊!
Lion, at least do it on the floor!
为啥总是在床上?
Why is it always on the bed?
魔法毛球宿命!
Magical hair-ball destiny!
好吧 恶心
Okay. That's gross.
好 不管怎样
Right. Anyway.
这把钥匙
This key.
妈妈肯定想要我现在得到它
Mom must have wanted you to give this to me now.
它是用来开什么的呢?
What does it open?
嗯...
Hm...
哦!
Oh!
嘿 狮子
Hey, Lion.
嗯?
Mm?
嗯
Mm.
嗯嗯!
Mmmm!
说不定我...
Maybe if I...
但是如果这把钥匙不是用来开箱子的 那它是用来干什么的呢?
If this key isn't for that chest, then what is it for?
这儿也没什么要打开的
Nothing to unlock here.
这儿也不对?
So, not here, either?
给我些能用钥匙打开的东西
Give me something this key unlocks.
嗯...
Hmm...
当然了!
Of course!
答案一直都在我身上!
The answers were inside me the whole time!
那我现在该去哪呢?
Where am I supposed to go?
这把钥匙肯定要打开什么的
This has to unlock something.
肯定还有我没去过的地方
There must be someplace I haven't been.
狮子
Lion.
带我去个新地点
Take me somewhere new.
嘿 拜托嘛
Hey, come on.
这个是从哪来的?
Where did you get this?
你能带我去那吗?
Can you please take me there?
求求你?
Pleeeeease?
求求...
Pleeeee...
...你?
...eeeease?
嘿 这儿是我们找到你的地方
Hey. This is where we found you.
妈妈藏了些东西在这儿, 对吧?
Something of Mom's is hidden here, right?
带我去那儿
Take me there.
我们要去哪?
Where are we going?
都已经几个小时了
It's been hours.
妈妈...你是谁?
Mom... who were you?
我又是谁?
Who am I?
石榴...
Garnet...
紫晶...
Amethyst...
珍珠...
Pearl...
她们虽然嘴上不说 但是...
They won't say it, but...
我知道她们对我期望很高
I know they expect something big from me.
但是我连自己的宿命都不知道 又怎么完成它呢
But how can I fulfill my destiny if I don't even know what it is?
我该成为什么呢?
Who am I supposed to be?
妈妈?
Mom?
这就是了
So this is it.
我们直接传送到这儿不好吗?
Couldn't we have just warped here?
无论这门后面是什么 我想一定很重要
Whatever's behind this door, I know it's something important.
求你告诉我我的宿命
Please tell me my destiny.
啥...?
Wha...?
啥?
What?
这是...玫瑰的垃圾堆?
Is this... just Rose's trash dump?
不
No.
别啊!
Please!
这儿肯定有些什么
There was supposed to be something here
有关我宿命的东西!
to tell me my purpose!
这就是堆妈妈留下的垃圾!
This is just a bunch of garbage Mom left behind!
哈?
Huh?
这是...妈妈的另一个录像带?
It's... another tape from Mom?
但是... 谁-谁是诺拉?
But... wh-who's Nora?
我-我不是独生子?
A-Am I not the only one?
我有个姐姐或妹妹?
Do I have a sister?
狮子!
Lion!
这是什么?
What is this?
谁-谁是诺拉?
W-Who's Nora?
我知道我已经要你做了很多事
I know I've asked a lot from you today,
但是求求你 再帮我一次
but please, just one more time.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
我想知道这个录像带的意义
I need to know what this tape means.
下次你吐在我床上我也不会生你气的
I won't get mad the next time you throw up on my bed.
这儿是海滩市附近啊
This is near Beach City.
狮子 你确定是这儿...
Lion, are you sure this is the right...
诺拉
Nora.
哦 嘿 史嘟宝
Oh, hey, Shtu-ball.
爸爸?! 你是诺拉?
Dad?! You're Nora?
谁?
Who?
你来这儿干嘛?
What are you doing here?
思考下我的歌怎么写
Getting some songs figured out.
啊 这儿算是我的创作小丘
Ah, this is sort of my jamming hill.
以前都是在仓库附近那棵树下创作
Used to be a tree by the warehouse,
但是那个七年级的笛子手把我给武力驱逐了
but a 7th-grader with a flute muscled me out.
呃...好吧
Uh... yeah.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
我找到了这个
I found this.
哦 我天
Oh, my gosh.
我都没想到还能再见到这个
I never thought I'd see this again.
你以前看过这个录像带?
You've seen this tape before?
当然了
Of course.
来这儿 你也该看看
Come here. You should, too.
他现在跟着我了!
He's following me now!
说不定这次他能帮你做片头呢
Maybe he'll help you with your intro this time.
爸爸?
Dad?
嘘!继续看
Shh! Keep watching.
准备...开始!
Okay... now!
人们称我...
They call me...
宇宙先生!
...Mr. Universe!
做好准备宝贝儿 因为你将会有
Get ready, baby, 'cause you're gonna have
这半边宇宙里最酷的老爹
the coolest dad this side of the cosmos.
这是...
This is...
现在按这个 对吧?
I press it now, right?
按就是了
Do it.
哇!格雷格?
Whoa! Greg?
我们把这段编辑下?
Can we edit this part?
不用 这样就很完美
No, no. It's perfect.
是不是很美妙 诺拉?
Isn't it wonderful, Nora?
这个世界有那么多可能性
This world is full of so many possibilities.
...给我的那个视频
...my video.
每个活物都有完全不同的独特体验
Each living thing has an entirely unique experience.
他们眼中的景色 他们体验的生活
The sights they see, the lives they live
都那么复杂...却又简单
are so complicated and... so simple.
这和妈妈留给我那个视频一样
This is just like the video Mom made me.
诺拉 我们不能同时存在
Nora, we can't both exist.
但我也不会离开
But I won't be gone.
我将会成为你的一半
I'm going to become half of you.
你享受成为自己的每一刻
And every moment you enjoy being yourself,
也都是我在热爱成为你
that will be me, loving being you.
不!我不明白
No! I don't understand.
为什么这个和你们给我的那个视频一模一样
Why is this the same as the video you guys made me?
诺拉又是谁?
Who's Nora?
诺-诺拉就是你啊
N-Nora is you.
我既是我妈妈又是我姊妹? !
I'm my mom and my sister?!
这算是哪门子宿命? !
What kind of destiny is this?!
不 不
No, no.
我们只是决定了两个名字
We just had it down to two names...
是个男孩就叫史蒂文 是个女孩就叫诺拉
Steven if you were a boy, and Nora if you were a girl.
所以 如果出生的不是我
So, then, would Nora have
那诺拉就会继承魔法宿命?
the magical destiny if I wasn't here?
魔法宿命? 这我可不知道
Magical destiny? I don't know about that.
但是妈妈知道啊!
But Mom did!
她在录像带里想告诉我什么的
She was trying to tell me something with my tape.
她一直给我留这些...谜题
She keeps leaving me... puzzle pieces.
迟早我要明白我存在的意义!
Sooner or later, I'm going to understand what I'm for!
哇!史蒂文 没关系的
Whoa! Steven, it's okay.
来 来这儿
Come here. Come here.
我本来应该...
Am I supposed to be...
她-她是想要我成为诺拉?
D-did she want me to be Nora?
史蒂文 她想要你成为你自己
Steven, she just wanted you to be you.
当你有了孩子 你根本想不到他会成为什么
When you have a kid, you have no idea who they're gonna be.
即便是石榴也不能预测
Even Garnet couldn't predict it.
你妈妈觉得
That's what was so exciting to your mom,
生活有无限可能 而你能亲自
that life is full of so many possibilities,
体验这些可能 这是最激动人心的
and you would get to explore them for yourself.
我是说 你能成为史蒂文或者诺拉或者任何人
I mean, you could be Steven or Nora or anyone else.
你也能随意改名字
And you can always change your name.
嘿 我就改了
Hey, I did.
因为你注定会成为非同寻常的存在
Because you're going to become something extraordinary.
你将会成为一个人类个体
You're going to be a human being.
这是我最爱的部分
That's my favorite part.
一个人类个体
A human being.
作为人类 是一种行为
A human is an action.
我好奇 你会成为谁 会怎么样
I wonder who, how you'll be,
你会思考些什么 你会渴求些什么
what you'll think, what you'll want.
哦 我也为你身边认识你的人感到高兴
Oh, I'm so happy for everyone who's going to know you.
我又在絮叨了
I'm rambling.
他们依靠你时 你要相信自己
If they look to you, trust yourself.
好好照顾他们 诺拉
Take care of them, Nora.
所以这就是我的宿命
So that's it.
我只是...注定要成为她的孩子
I'm just... supposed to be her kid.
这个...是啊
Well... yeah.
这不好吗?
Is that okay?
这很好
Yeah.
我想我能做到的
I think I can handle that.